const t=[{question:"Which keyword is used to create an object in C#?",options:["new","create","init","instance"],correctOption:0,points:10},{question:"Which method is called when an object is created in C#?",options:["Initialize","Constructor","Create","Build"],correctOption:1,points:10},{question:"Which of the following is a value type in C#?",options:["String","Object","int","Array"],correctOption:2,points:10},{question:"What does the 'static' keyword mean in C#?",options:["The class can only have one instance","The class cannot be inherited","The method or variable belongs to the class itself rather than instances","The method is only accessible within its own assembly"],correctOption:2,points:10},{question:"Which keyword is used for inheritance in C#?",options:["inherits","extend","base",":"],correctOption:3,points:10},{question:"What is the default access modifier for class members in C#?",options:["public","private","protected","internal"],correctOption:1,points:10},{question:"What is the purpose of the 'using' keyword in C#?",options:["To create a namespace","To import types from a namespace","To declare a local variable","To define a loop"],correctOption:1,points:30},{question:"Which of the following is NOT a C# access modifier?",options:["protected","internal","secure","private"],correctOption:2,points:20},{question:"What is the output of the following code: Console.WriteLine(5 / 2);",options:["2","2.5","2.0","3"],correctOption:0,points:20},{question:"How do you handle exceptions in C#?",options:["try-catch","catch-finally","handle-exception","try-finally"],correctOption:0,points:30},{question:"What is a delegate in C#?",options:["A variable that stores data","A reference type that holds references to methods","A keyword to declare abstract classes","A method to handle exceptions"],correctOption:1,points:30},{question:"Which method is used to convert a string to an integer in C#?",options:["Convert.ToInt32()","int.Parse()","Both A and B","StringToInt()"],correctOption:2,points:10},{question:"What is LINQ in C#?",options:["A library for networking","A framework for building user interfaces","A language feature for querying collections","A method for parsing JSON data"],correctOption:2,points:30},{question:"An interface can contain:",options:["Methods with implementation","Fields","Static methods","Method signatures"],correctOption:3,points:30},{question:"What is the purpose of the 'async' keyword in C#?",options:["To define a synchronous method","To create a thread","To indicate that a method contains asynchronous operations","To handle exceptions"],correctOption:2,points:20}],e={questions:t};export{e as default,t as questions};
